<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="questions_array">
        <item>How will you feel about your problem and what will you think about it tomorrow?
            In five years?  In twenty years?  In forty years?</item>
        <item>What sort of people would tackle a problem like yours easily?</item>
        <item>If this problem came up with someone dear to you, what would you advise them?</item>
        <item>When you are concentrating on your problem, are you distinguishing between what is
            important and what is secondary? Are you really focused on the main point?</item>
        <item>In order to resolve the problem at hand – you need strength.  What gives you strength?</item>
        <item>Is your interpretation of the problem objective and accurate?</item>
        <item>Where do your motives come from?</item>
        <item>If someone you admire were coping with this problem, how would they go about it?</item>
        <item>What advantages (even small ones) could this problem have?</item>
        <item>Could it be that you ascribe more importance to the matter than it really deserves?</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="country">
        <item>United States</item>
        <item>Israel</item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="questions_explanations_array">
        <item>"Sorry its really clear - no need for explanation"</item>
        <item>When you understand what types of people would tackle this sort of problem easily, try to imitate them,
            do it as an \“act\” – only outwardly.  Try to keep up the \“act\” over several hours.
            What does it feel like?  What did you learn from this experience?</item>
        <item>Sometimes it is easier for us to advise others, but harder to advise ourselves. Try to
            imagine that you have friend who is distressed over the same sort of thing that you are now struggling with.
            Try to think what sort of advice you would give your friend and then try to act on it yourself.</item>
        <item>Our lives are full of details.  Some of them come under the heading of \“important\” and some under that of \“secondary\”.
            Like most people you also have limited amounts of energy, and therefore you must understand what is most important,
            concentrate on this and give it all of your attention.  What is \“important\” in your problem?</item>
        <item>Think of times when you felt strong, of things that you did that sent positive energy flowing through you.
            How and when can you connect to a \“generator\” like that?
            If that specific \“generator\” is no longer relevant, you must come up with a plan of action to build a new one.
            Think, what could you do to send new energy to your system right now?</item>
        <item>The problem itself is one matter, and the interpretation we give it is another.  Unfortunately,
            we sometimes confuse the objective problem with the subjective feelings we feel about it and create something hybrid.
            For instance:  Being fired from your job is a genuine and serious problem and can lead to economic hardship.
            But it isn\’t proof of your lack of ability, lack of intelligence or lack of success in life.
            Even if your boss acted cruelly when firing you, and insulted you terribly – you still have to assume that
            you simply didn\’t meet the requirements of the job or the mentality of the workplace.
            There is no reason to think that being fired from this job is proof that you are a \“failure\” or a \“loser\”.
            We need to separate the objective occurrence:  \“I was fired\” and the damage to our self-esteem: \“I\’m not successful.\”
            Think honestly – could you find a cleaner pair of \“glasses,\” less emotional ones, through which you could view the problem?
            Where could you find an \“optometrist\’s shop\” (a good book or advisor) in which to exchange your old glasses for newer and more efficient ones?
        </item>
        <item>Are most of your motives coming from good places such as: a desire to succeed, a desire to make a living,
            a desire to realize your potential, to improve, etc, or are they coming from negative places such as: a desire to get even,
            greed, etc.?
            It would be good if you can go deeper into your own motives and make sure you like them.
            This sort of self-clarification can surprise you and change your entire perspective!
        </item>
        <item>Think of a person you admire very much, and try to imagine how they would look at an issue like that which you face now.
            What is the first thing they would do?  How would they view the problem?  What would they do to help themselves?
            What could you learn from them if you were to discuss the problem with them?
            Try to imagine having this discussion and see what they suggest.
        </item>
        <item>There\’s no good without bad and there\’s no bad without good.
            I\’m almost positive you can find plusses or opportunities in your problem as well.
         (Remember, even being wiser is a great advantage; often, troubles make us wiser and richer in life experience.)
        </item>
        <item>Perhaps there is a way to reduce the volume of space this subject is taking up inside of you?
            Surely in the past you\’ve had difficult emotions and after some time had past you
            realized you had exaggerated the situation.  Could this be one of those times?</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>